<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Manali</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="things">Things to do</string>
    <string name="places">Places to visit</string>
    <string name="food">Local food</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="paragliding">Paragliding</string>
    <string name="rafting">River Rafting</string>
    <string name="camping">Riverside Camp</string>
    <string name="balloon">Balloon Ride</string>
    <string name="igloo_stay">Igloo Stay</string>
    <string name="hadimba">Hadimba Devi Temple</string>
    <string name="manu">Manu Temple</string>
    <string name="solang">Solang Valley</string>
    <string name="mall">Mall Road</string>
    <string name="zostel">Zostel Manali</string>
    <string name="orchards">Orchards House</string>
    <string name="club">White Meadows</string>
    <string name="hotel">New Harmony Inn</string>
    <string name="babru">Babru</string>
    <string name="siddu">Siddu</string>
    <string name="bhey">Bhey</string>
    <string name="chha">Chha Ghost</string>
    <string name="tibetan">Tibetan Thukpa</string>
    <string name="manali">Discover the enchanting allure of Manali, nestled amidst the majestic Himalayas. Embark on thrilling adventures like paragliding and river rafting, or simply soak in the tranquility of pine-scented forests and cascading waterfalls. Explore the vibrant streets of Old Manali, brimming with charming cafes and bustling markets. Whether seeking adrenaline rushes or serene moments, Manali offers an unforgettable journey of wonder and discovery amidst breathtaking landscapes.</string>
    <string name="paraglidingDetail">Enjoy the thrill of paragliding in the Himalayan sky while admiring Manali from a bird\'s eye view. Gliding in the middle of snow-capped peaks, open blue sky, and magical vistas of the valleys surrounding you will be a once-in-a-lifetime experience. Under the guidance of a professional instructor, engage in this amazing activity and ensure that it is a memorable adventure!</string>
    <string name="raftingDetail">River rafting in Manali is one adrenaline-pumping recreation that draws adventure seekers from all over the country. A thrilling experience awaits you as you embark upon the meandering course of the Beas River. The stunning scenery flanked on both sides of the river is another spectacle to behold while you maneuver your raft along the calm waters.</string>
    <string name="campingDetail">Escape into the tranquil embrace of nature with our riverside camping experience in Manali! Nestled amidst the breathtaking Himalayan landscape, indulge in a serene getaway along the banks of pristine rivers. Immerse yourself in the soothing melody of flowing waters, under the starlit sky, and indulge in outdoor adventures while creating unforgettable memories. Experience an unforgettable journey in the heart of the mountains.</string>
    <string name="balloonDetail">Hot air ballooning in Manali is a thrilling experience and a must-try. Manali being a beautiful hill station offering a scenic view makes the experience more enthralling. Embark in this exciting activity in Manali together along with your partners and have fun by taking selfies and shooting stunning bird\'s eye view pictures from 300 ft above the ground level. Avail this Hot Air Balloon Trip in Manali and revel in the stunning perspectives from 300 ft above ground level. Embark in this activity and float in the vast sky with your partners and build memories.</string>
    <string name="igloo_stayDetail">Nestled cosily in the snow-capped mountains of the mystic Sethan valley, this campsite is perched at a whopping altitude of around 10,000 feet from sea level. This whole zone is marked by white sheets and views of mountains all around. Indulge in a unique and absolutely breathtaking stay experience at an igloo. With delicious meals and various snow-related activities, this activity is a must for all those seeking the comfort of the snow and cold.</string>
    <string name="hadimbaDetail">Hidimba Devi Temple, locally known as Dhungari Temple, also known variously as the Hadimba Temple. It is an ancient cave temple dedicated to Hidimbi Devi, wife of Bhima, a figure in the Indian epic Mahabharata. The temple is surrounded by a cedar forest called Dhungiri Van Vihar at the foot of the Himalayas. The sanctuary is built over a huge rock jutting out of the ground which was worshiped as an image of the deity. The structure was built in 1553 by Maharajah Bahadur Singh.</string>
    <string name="manuDetail">Manu Temple, a beautiful temple dedicated to Sage Manu. The temple lies in the Beas River Valley, in Kullu District which is about 275 kilometres North of Shimla. The topographical features of the valley are inviting, and trekkers all over the world are drawn to Manali. It has been a tourist attraction for quite some years, and travellers wanting to come closer to the divine powers of Indian deities usually come here seeking peace and to be spiritually enlightened. As one explores the region, they are sure to notice the calmness around the beautiful Manu Temple.</string>
    <string name="solangDetail">Solang Valley derives its name from a combination of the words Solang (Nearby village) and Nallah (water stream). It is a side valley at the top of the Kullu Valley, 14 km northwest of Manali on the way to Rohtang Pass, and is known for its summer and winter sports conditions. The sports most commonly offered are parachuting, paragliding, skating, and zorbing.</string>
    <string name="mallDetail">Mall Road is the main street in Manali. The offices of municipal corporation, fire service, and police headquarters are located here. Automobiles, except emergency vehicles are not allowed on this road.</string>
    <string name="zostelDetail">Zostel Manali (Old Manali) is set amidst a dreamy landscape of snow-capped mountains, apple orchards, and rustic wooden houses. Located in the backpacker hub of Old Manali, the hostel is one of the most happening places in town. The premise also houses The Garden Café, which serves authentic Himachali with other delicacies. With activities like snowboarding, and paragliding, or a low-key hike shared with your hostel gang watching the sunset, Manali calls out to adventure and mountain lovers alike.</string>
    <string name="orchardsDetail">Featuring a balcony with mountain views, a garden and a shared lounge, Orchards House - The Hidden Tribe can be found in Manāli, close to Hidimba Devi Temple and 1.6 km from Circuit House. Boasting full-day security, this property also provides guests with an outdoor fireplace. The accommodation provides a hot spring bath, free WiFi throughout the property and family rooms.</string>
    <string name="clubDetail">Life becomes richer thanks to the experiences we provide. At Club Mahindra White Meadows Manali, Himachal Pradesh, you find a lavish spread of offerings for every family member. With each daybreak, new adventures begin. Connect with nature and your inner being.</string>
    <string name="hotelDetail">Hotel New Harmony Inn is a luxurious stay in Manali, with travel guides and all facilities, the hotel is close to all tourist destinations and… There\'s nothing like coming Manali after a long work day to Stay in your favorite Hotel. If you spend a lot of time in Holidays, you should make sure that you Stay in "Quality Hotel New Harmony Inn". A well chosen Hotel can make all the difference in your Holidays &amp; Vacations with family, friend and group.</string>
    <string name="babruDetail">Babru looks kinda similar to a North Indian dish, known as kachori but you will find a striking difference between the flavours of both dishes. This flattened bread is prepared with wheat flour. The flavourful filling of black gram paste makes it an impressive dish of Himachal Pradesh. This delicacy is served with tamarind chutney and a nice cup of hot tea to provide a soothing experience in Himachal’s freezing cold temperature.</string>
    <string name="sidduDetail">Siddu is basically a bun with an amazing filling. The dish is made with a dough of wheat flour and is filled with fat to make it extra special. The dough is then roasted for a while. The dough is further steamed until the dough is ready to eat. That’s it! You can have Siddu now with vegetables or mutton to make it taste even better.</string>
    <string name="bheyDetail">Bhey is a crispy Himachal Pradesh dish with finger-licking flavours. The dish is prepared with Lotus stem which is cooked in ginger, garlic, onion, gram flour, and other Indian spices to get the authentic flavour. You can enjoy Bhey with roti, parathas, and even rice. If you had just one bite, then you probably can’t resist having more. Bhey is so satisfying that even your kids will surely be obsessed with it.</string>
    <string name="chhaDetail">Chha Gosht is for people who are always ready to enjoy non-veg dishes. Chha Gosht is one of the best non-veg dishes in Himachal Pradesh which is prepared by marinating lamb for a short period. The marination is further cooked in ginger-garlic paste, yogurt, gram flour, and some flavourful Indian spices such as a bay leaf, asafoetida, cardamom powder, coriander powder, and red chili powder. If you wish to try the best Chha Gosht in Himachal Pradesh, then head to the Chamba district of Himachal Pradesh.</string>
    <string name="tibetanDetail">Himachal Pradesh is a Tibetan-influenced state. As a result, you will find the popular Tibetan dish, Thukpa, at every restaurant in Himachal Pradesh. Thukpa is a noodle soup that is available in both vegetarian and non-vegetarian options. A vegetarian Thukpa is loaded with vegetables such as carrots, onions, tomatoes, and cabbage. One cup of piping hot Thukpa will bring you so much comfort and warmth in the freezing cold weather of Himachal Pradesh. Dharamshala is the place where you can get the best authentic Tibetan Thukpas.</string>
</resources>